got what happened to me so tell me a
little bit about that and I'll let you I
know that you're trying to get their
laptop up so I'll give you some time to
no sorry I got some I know I
um so I if you I'll answer that question
first and I would love to get on here
because I know a couple of people are
asking questions so um for me that post
was really about being completely rooted
in who you are and the importance of
knowing who you are and I know that
sounds so simple but it's really really
deep because often times the second you
declare who you are the opposition will
come and tell you that you're not that
the second that you say this is what I'm
going to do you're going to get people
doubting you the second you you start
your journey is the second people are
going to call you crazy what are you
doing how could you do this you're not
that why are you doing this and you're
going to get criticized and oftentimes
it's from the people that love you that
are quote unquote supposed to love you
the most or the people that you respect
the most or the people that are closest
to you and for me a situation happened
that um in my journey I have a very
small amount of people in my family that
are just those Avid supporters and I
love them to bit and there's a lot of
the other people that are well when you
fall on your face don't come back or
when you do this you're gonna fail
you're and it's it's that constant thing
and when you don't remind yourself of
who you are which will happen there will
be a moment that you get caught off
guard that you know you're going through
something and you're not aware of it and
you step into a situation and and you
don't mentally prepare yourself and
that's why I'm huge on priming your mind
feeding your mind good things every
single day because doubt will always
come fear will always show up criticism
will always be there and if you stand
guard on on your mind and your heart
you're able to deal with those things
better so I recently walked into a
situation and I was not I was not just
prepared for that situation and it hit
me it's like the dagger normally melt
away but this one this one was like oh I
wasn't ready for that and I came home
and I ended up speaking to um one of the
people that I just I love chatting to
about business and he was talking to me
he's like where did you go like who is
this person that I'm talking to so I
wanted to sh share that because it's I
want to show the vulnerability in it
that we all go through this that I'm not
this perfect person that is like living
my Soulful hustle and living my dreams
and never going through doubt never
going through hardship never going
through anything because it will always
come and just the methods that I do to
prepare myself for that wow W um yeah
I'm having a great so I just I love I'm
having a great time I love every answer
you you you say it so beautifully and
and and you highlight oh thank you you
you you you highlight just the you
know you highlight a part that a lot of
people Miss it's like we we're so hard
on ourselves you know we're so we are
you know we want to push through we want
to be on top but it's it's like you
don't have to take that big leap you
could take small steps you know you dig
yourself in the hole but you can create
steps back out you know and um you know
you just have to let things you got to
let things flow you're not going to make
everybody happy and you are going to get
people yeah go
ahead I was going to say I I'm just
sharing this on my
wall um and I'm reading some of the
comments but what I was going to say is
welcome to the hustle Zone hey guess
what folks I know I like I you know this
whole hustle Zone thing when I'm like
welcome to the hustle Zone I was
honestly making a joke I had my
assistant here and I was like welcome to
the power Zone and I was just playing
around and then it just it's just one of
those things that stuck and that's
awesome so folks I want to bring on
someone that I I just met but did some
research saw some some of her videos and
there's one thing
about about my guest that you don't
really see in other entrepreneurs
especially those who are coaches she
brings the
soul into
entrepreneurialism and a I love it often
often times we don't really like we just
think it's go go go go go and just you
know power through energy and when you
watch her videos it's laidback she
brings like a balance to you know brings
a a sense of peace to you being an
entrepreneur and that's what I
appreciate about uh uh about you and
about what I've seen so far and so folks
I would like to welcome Leah no terani
did I get the last you got it right
awesome I love it so awesome so yeah
like I I mean I watched your videos and
and I was like man you know you're
pretty insightful and uh so I definitely
most definitely like and I I'm going to
tell my audience that the hustle Z is
about capturing the spirit of the
entrepreneur so it was like it was like
a match made in heaven that you know
she's Soulful and I'm talking about the
spirit because a lot of people don't
really understand the spirit of the
entrepreneur they only see the fast cars
they see the lifestyle
and everybody wants the the the material
wealth but they don't see the the the
amount of struggle the sacrifices and
and all that that go into
entrepreneurialism so anyway welcome how
are you doing thank you so much for
having me you know what I love that I I
saw your post and it said who wants to
be on the hustle and I was like oh my
God hustle yes so thank you so much for
having me I appreciate that and I love
that little introduction that you did so
for me um I do several I do have several
different businesses and I am a complete
entrepreneur I love entrepreneurship and
building people up and what I found with
building businesses and building teams
and doing different things that there
was a part that I found that people
struggle the most with and that was
finding that that balance within the
Soulful side of staying connected to who
you are the personal development the
digging deep within you to really figure
out what is my purpose what am I here to
do give and be and then also it goes on
the opposite end of the spectrum that
some people just hustle hustle hustle
and they lose their connection with self
and what I really did was how do we
marry these two amazing things together
because we need both we need the
strategy you need the hard work you need
all of those things but you also need
the Soulful side you need to dig deep
within yourself because I always believe
that um your business will never outgrow
your personal development so we need to
be constantly growing and evolving and
and digging deep and figuring out what
are our strengths what are our
weaknesses and building a business based
on that
wow wow that's pretty deep and and it
honestly it is it is I don't do surface
level it's like woo we cut deep we're
like I'm I'm swimming with the fishes
right now how deep this is you know this
is good I think we're going to have a
really good so awesome this is the
Church of Leah so we're gonna it's
Sunday you know it's time to relax but
it's time Soulful Sundays and um okay so
the first question that I have to ask
and and I I I can't wait to ask you this
question especially asking you um
because you the concept of of being a
soul Soulful Hustler is so deep already
but I it begs the question how did you
come up with that idea so most of the
times I ask this question what is your
story you know like tell me from the
beginning we have all day tell us how
how did you become to be who you are um
like what was the struggles the things
that you had to go through to kind of
get to that level of
deepness that's a really good question
and that's a long long answer um because
a lot of people ask me like Leah how did
you get started from where you were
and I guess I could bring it back to
when I was in my 20s I had my first
daughter so I'm a single parent I have
two young beautiful girls I have a
9-year-old and a two and a half-year-old
and I kind of did everything backwards
than what would be considered
traditional I had a daughter at the age
of 20 I started my first career as a
general manager by the age of
22 I became the top general manager and
I was always in involved with leadership
and development
and I ended up getting into a car
accident so I was at really amazing
point in my career and I got in a car
accident
and I got hit from behind from a vehicle
I was at a dead stop on the highway
because the traffic was backed up and I
got hit by 80 kilometers an hour so yeah
so I suffered from severe severe
Whiplash and back pain and to make that
long story short in essence I had to go
off work and go through severe
Rehabilitation to basically rebuild my
the strength in my back and my neck and
everything was a mess and through that I
ended up losing my job which was a very
well-paying job and it was in that
moment that I realized that I needed to
own my own life that anything can happen
in a moment and that was really
something in me that I said I need to be
able to to build and create what I've
been able to do for in the corporate
world at such a young age and I guess my
whole life it was always just different
struggles after struggles after
struggles and losing your job and then
not being able to physically work for a
short period of time and then going back
to school and doing all of these
different things and then coming into
entrepreneurship and building a business
and for me just being around people and
always working with people for so long
that it it as I buil the as I built my
last business um I realized that there's
a side that you need to stay true to who
you are and how to strategically do that
so what led me to soulful Hustlers is a
year ago I made the decision to be
completely unapologetically
authentically myself and I learned to
say no to the businesses that I didn't
like yes to the opportunities that I
wanted and through that I said there's
so many women out there that are sitting
at home struggling with who am I what am
I here to do and what am I here to give
and that gap between staying connected
and knowing yourself and then giving
yourself the Strategic plan plan in
order to execute it was missing and
after coaching and
developing um women I was in a network
marketing business previously like I've
done so many different things I I just
saw this massive Gap and I said people
need this people need to know how to
stay connected to themsel and to do that
and for me that's when I learn because
often times people come to me and say
how are you doing this business how are
you running a business with two children
in a new city in a new country doing XY
Z and then how are you confident and it
all comes back to that it all comes back
to that ability to figure out what your
Soulful hustle is
so I don't know if that answered your
question that that was like I I got I
got value and then I got more value so I
was like man I feel like I have to
pay you for all of that information that
you gave me no I know no sorry so I know
a lot of people say like what are your
what is your big story and it's such a
deep one that it's it's been crazy like
even in a nutshell in one year I you
know there's so much that's happened
that I think I've been told several
times that I need to write a book so I'm
gonna probably end up doing that because
there's so many little elements to it
because in my journey I I want to share
and say if I can do it you can do it cuz
I've been thrown through the mud and if
there's I've been through so much as a
woman as an entrepreneur that trust me
if I can do it you can do it and that
will be my message to um to share that
so with all of those things I will put
that out and you will be the one of the
first people to know when it's there
awesome well you know I can say that um
you know there's a lot of every every
entrepreneurs is unique right and and
the one thing that connects us all is
our story you know for for me to just
look at you you're a beautiful woman and
I think that most most most people would
look at you and said hey well she had it
easy you know she's
talented so like what do you do you do
you get that you probably often get that
and people just misjudging you because
they think that your your looks probably
got you where you are today or that is
such an amazing thing that you just said
I love that you're bringing that up so
thank you yeah so you know let let talk
about that like you know do do you have
such good question do you have an easy I
don't so I built everything that I've
ever had completely on my own I was
never given a silver spoon growing up um
there's a lot of background story to
that I was living in and out on my own
by the age of 16 I had a child by the
age of 20 that I raised completely on my
own um I ended up climbing the corporate
ladder I worked 18 hours a day just to
support my child I ended up getting
physically harmed in a car accident that
there was nothing I could do about it
that led me to move seven times in two
years wow I um you name it like I've
I've I've been through a lot and a lot
of people can say you know what you're
you know you're pretty you can just do
it or things like that and that
oftentimes for me it's like I because of
that it was actually the quite opposite
I had to prove myself even more so when
I went to one of my first careers as
being a manager or running a
multi-million dollar facility I was
going in there as this young
female and I had to prove myself that I
was worthy of that job and you're not
just getting a job because you're pretty
so what I ended up doing is I ended up
going to work at a women's only facility
and I ended up being the top general
manager I crushed my goal I hit like
150% of the the company's quota in the
first month just to prove a point wow
and I had to go and speak in front of
150 other general managers explaining to
them what I did in my first month in my
first month I was actually hired as the
assistant manager and I got promoted
within a month and took over somebody's
maternity leave and she's like you're
you're going to crush it here and I did
so it's always been the exact opposite
so I've
always made it a point to prove myself
and as women this is something that I I
share often is you need to be somebody
of
like how do I say this with you know I'm
never I'm very raw and real so just say
it just be
raw if you are
this you need to
be it's the inner beauty it's all of
those things that matter so much more
this this shell the spacit whatever you
want to call it that's
great but for me it was always about
enriching other people's lives and some
people might be attracted to the outer
shell which is a little bit shallow but
that's sometimes the way that the world
Works however when people truly get to
know me they're like wow you're you're
deep you you have value
you and that's why I've been able to
build a business because if I were to
say I built a business on my looks I
would have been a model but I'm not I'm
a business strategist so people hire me
to go in there and maximize their
business and people go in there to hire
me to build their teams so I've made it
a point to prove myself that you know
what I'm not just a pretty face because
if I wanted to be at when I was around
22 23 I was offered contracts for um
different agencies when I was in the
fitness industry and I had some meetings
with like magazines and stuff for just
for female fitness like wellness very
classy but well
and um I denied all of those for the
simple reason of what you just asked me
wow yeah wow just I can't I can't do it
and everyone's been like Leah you should
do this you're amazing like you've
worked out your whole life and I was
like no because that's not the image
that I want to perceive in this world
that is not the message that I want to
share to my beautiful young girls that
you're beautiful and that's it there's
so much more woo you know and and like
that that that goes to you know like me
being a black male and my voice not
being as deep as other brothers like you
know like it's like I Tred like what's
up baby you know but it doesn't work
uh got to be you I have to be me right
so when I was growing up and I was I was
I was managing and and whatnot it was
really hard for people to take me
seriously because I look like I'm 16
years old and um you know I've had to I
I can agree with you I'm not I'm not um
near I'm not pretty at all but you know
I'm like the opposite you're so funny
but I um you know but I still had to
prove myself and I think that you know
that's what the whole thing about
entrepreneurialism is because you're
always when you are trying to do
something that's new or something that's
great you're always going to have people
that's going to push you down or push
you back and um my whole life yeah
absolutely so I um just from what you
were saying I find it very interesting
that you know you were 22 and you
already had the business acen to to
strive for excellence where does a
22-year-old get that idea from like how
did that was that instilled did you have
great parenting or you know like what
was what what gave you that that ability
to to be so successful at such a young
age that's a really great question so I
think that
either disappointment in life will
either drive or destroy you and for me
it drove me to be the absolute best
version of myself so I from a very young
age for me remember before I actually
came out to California I was going
through my old staff and I found a
trophy from when I was a gymnast and it
was it sounds super silly but it said
the most determined my entire life I've
always been extremely driven so it was
um not a driven that I was competing
against other people but competing with
myself so I needed to always be the best
version of me and from a young age I was
very ambitious I knew that I wanted to
make a change in the world I didn't
really know what that looked like and
that's why it's taken me several years
to get to the point that now I know
exactly who I am and I teach people how
to go on that Journey as well so to help
answer your question I think that um I I
just went for it like I always I never I
didn't hold back and I put myself in
positions that you know what maybe I
wouldn't have been in and I just I
constantly pushed and strove and had
this incredibly high standard for myself
that the standard was so high for myself
that you know other people's standards
were cool but mine was like super high
so now I'm going to get a little bit
personal okay um being an entrepreneur
in a single dad single dad meaning MH
dating dad so you must you're single mom
and I found dating a challenge uh and
again this folks I want you guys to like
and share this broadcast because
honestly this is the this is one of the
deepest conversations that I've had on
on the hustle zone so far and I love it
you know so much we definitely got the
soul in this Sunday so folks please like
and share I just want to acknowledge
people that are in this broadcast ready
we got Patrick V yeah cuz I can't see
the comments I would love to see them I
should pull up my laptop uh and if you
would like to pull up your laptop go
right on ahead you know I love the
interaction with the guests uh we got
Carlos Phoenix in the house yeah I would
love that I got to find it I'm GNA bring
you guys for a little walk awesome as we
gots we got Al love to hear from you we
got Josh con we have Douglas
Alman uh we have Wade blood good so
folks thank you guys for tuning in we
got nine likes and Carlos says that I'm
ugly a that's not very nice but we're
about to get deep here we're about to
get really deep okay so love it we're
talking about dating as entrepreneurs
first problem that I have is having time
to date I don't have the time you know
so it's like if I meet someone I really
need to tune in to you we need to
connect cuz if we don't
I'm it if I'm going to take those hours
that I have to go on a date it be worth
it right so true absolutely and
absolutely the other thing is you know
being a single father and then having to
split the time with my kid and with the
person I'm dating and having the person
feel that they are being left
out right right that's that's that's
curse number two well I wouldn't call it
a curse but it's the what people will
perceive as a curse the third thing is
being
um too
confident like H being uh you know being
too confident being accomplished and
having the person feel that they don't
have their self worth you know they
don't feel that they they measure up so
on those three things you can choose
either one or you can choose all three
but how how was dating as a single mom
being an entrepreneur that's that's a
good question so um I was married before
so I had a short-lived marriage and I've
recently been divorced so for
me that's different
because it has to be something I clearly
you know that I'm super deep and of
substance so for me it needs to be like
how do you find that balance is how you
find anything in life it's you will put
the time and effort into into something
that matters you will always make time
but um to balance that is is the same
way you'd kind of balance your the time
that you have with your children you
figure out even as a busy entrepreneur
even though that this is truthfully the
mission of why I was put on this Earth
was to do what I'm doing now I I know
that within every fiber of my being and
even with that when you first start out
is figuring out what are the things that
mean the most to me is family important
to you is is being in a committed
relationship important to you it's
finding that significant other important
to you and if all of those things are
important to you it's figuring out if
you hold up your calendar what's
important to you and you can't see that
time in there with your kids or your
significant other then it's never going
to work right so as a busy entrepreneur
you just have
to find that balance of who's important
to you and how to make that work and
have you had any challenges cuz I guess
you're saying that you were newly
divorced but have you had any challenges
in in the dating world or is that a
focus for you right now you know what
it's just not a focus for me right now I
am
so
just engulfed in my work right now that
this is
like this lights me up and I I believe
that everything um happens for a reason
you'll meet certain people for a reason
and when the time is right the time will
be right and I I have faith in all of
those things so I don't actively Force
things like that so I just stay open and
just be and be oh I love that you know
just be you know because every other
living thing in this world just is just
there it grows you know and being
yourself and not really putting that's
the beauty of entrepreneurialism is that
we can be who we want to be you know we
can live Our Truth we can tell people
how we feel and there is I believe that
there's a spiritual component to
entrepreneurialism uh because what we're
doing is
creation you know yeah you're literally
creating you're creating the world that
you want to live in you're creating
everything yes and and you're creating
things for other people around you so
you have to be at a positive point in
your life and if you are in Conflict
it's really hard for you to um and
that's why I notice a lot of
entrepreneurs they like to they control
their
environment and you had a
video talking about just that and I went
on your um on your uh uh your website
and you were with a bunch of people that
were just had a different frequency and
then that frequency rubbed off on you
and then you decided that oh my God what
happened to me so tell me a little bit
about that and I'll let you I know that
you're trying to get their laptop up so
I'll give you some time no sorry I got
some I know I
um so I if you I'll answer that question
first and I would love to get on here
because I know a couple of people are
asking questions so um for me that post
was really about being completely rooted
in who you are and the importance of
knowing who you are and I know that
sounds so simple but it's really really
deep because often times the second you
declare who you are the opposition will
come and tell you that you're not that
the second that you say this is what I'm
going to do you're going to get people
doubting you the second you you start
your journey is the second people are
going to call you crazy what are you
doing how could you do this you're not
that why are you doing this and you're
going to get criticized and oftentimes
it's from the people that love you that
are quote unquote supposed to love you
the most or the people that you respect
the most or the people that are closest
to you and for me a situation happened
that um in my journey I have a very
small amount of people in my family that
are just those Avid supporters and I
love them to bits and there's a lot of
the other people that are well when you
fall on your face don't come back or
when you do this you're gonna fail
you're and it's it's that constant thing
and when you don't remind yourself of
who you are which will happen there will
be a moment that you get caught off
guard that you know you're going through
something and you're not aware of it and
you step into a situation and and you
don't mentally prepare yourself and
that's why I'm huge on priming your mind
feeding your mind good things every
single day because doubt will always
come fear will always show up criticism
will always be there and if you stand
guard on on your mind and your heart
you're able to deal with those things
better so I recently walked into a
situation and I was not I was not just
prepared for that situation and it hit
me it's like the daggers normally melt
away but this one this one was like oh I
wasn't ready for that and I came home
and I ended up speaking to um one of the
people that I just I love chatting to
about business and he was talking to me
he's like where did you go like who was
this person that I'm talking to so I
wanted to sh share that because it's I
want to show the vulnerability in it
that we all go through this that I'm not
this perfect person that is like living
my Soulful hustle and living my dreams
and never going through doubt never
going through hardship never going
through anything because it will always
come and just the methods that I do to
prepare myself for that
wow yeah I'm having a great so I just I
love I'm having a great time I love
every answer you you you say it so
beautifully and and and you highlight oh
thank you you you you you highlight just
the you
know you highlight a part that a lot of
people Miss it's like we we're so hard
on ourselves you know we're we are you
know we want to push through we want to
be on top but it's it's like you don't
have to take that big leap you could
take small steps you know you dig
yourself in a hole but you can create
steps back out you know and um you know
you just have to let things you got to
let things flow you're not going to make
everybody happy and you are going to get
people yeah go ahead
I was going to say I I'm just sharing
this on my
wall um and I'm reading some of the
comments but what I was going to say is
I even did another entire article about
this because this is something that we
truly as human beings told we I did an
article and it was about um ambition
versus approval yeah and we're like that
recognition and that you know what I
mean that constant sense for that uh
know you're enough and that approval of
others sometimes will outweigh what
we're truly meant to do right I and I
can say that I I used to be a rapper
when I was young and the first when f
Facebook came out I would get everyone
to be I would put my music out there and
get everyone to like it and be like tell
me what you think about it and then
people would be like right you know what
I didn't like the way that you layed
those stairs I think you don't know how
to or I think that you do this you do
that and then I got to a point where I
was like you know what I'm just not
going to ask you for your guys's
opinion not because I don't want I
because I feel like anyone at any time
can find something negative to say and I
think you know they absolutely can you
know I can talk about the Sun and say ah
it's too hot you know ah the sun is too
bright you know we can always find but
there's not enough people out there
saying things that you're doing positive
and and I think that when you try like
you said when you want to do something
that is um ambitious you know people try
to look within themselves and if they
think that they can't achieve it they
automatically put that on you and say no
you it's that projection it's like no no
no no no I can you can't because that's
something you're not willing to do
because I said I want to be a
billionaire oh you can't be a
billionaire well you can't be a
billionaire but I want to that's yeah
it's the effect right and people often
project their insecurities on other
people and one thing that I I often
share people that are in
entrepreneurship or getting into their
own business is there comes a place that
you can't rely on other people to
believe in you you need to believe in
yourself and that was the game Cher for
me I stopped waiting for everybody to
believe that I was able to do it I
stepped up believed in myself and went
and and went and did it and when you go
from that position of
strength I everybody was here everybody
on this Earth was created for a purpose
everybody the leaves on the trees to the
ants on the ground every single thing is
created here for a reason and the second
you find that reason and you believe in
your own abilities
and believe in in a reason that you were
here there's a reason why you're here
and you truly believe believe that and
you stay true to that it's amazing what
doors will open for you yeah yeah so I'm
going to read some of these comments
Carlos Phoenix says do it I got I'm hard
on myself hard not to get caught up in
failures always tough to overcome that
and focus on being a business person
yeah I can agree with that Carlos oh I
love that yeah I I'm just to add to that
yeah oh sir no go ahead no go ahead
there's a there seems to be a lag folks
but that's okay go ahead it's um what I
was going to say is for Carlos is
getting caught up with failure first of
all the word failure itself you have to
Define what is failure because for me if
I were to look at quote unquote my
failed relationships my failed quote
unquote businesses whatever those things
were it's truthfully their learning
experiences they they're what brings you
that's the tuition you pay for being an
entrepreneur
and um sorry I just got a call there um
so that's the tuition you pay for being
an entrepreneur that we don't know how
to do everything imagine if we knew how
to do everything in this world nothing
would be exciting anymore we would just
go and know how to do everything but
with failure it's when I look at
something that didn't go the way that I
wanted to or I made a decision that I
probably won't make again our our
success is actually built upon failures
we fail quote unquote if you want to use
that word if I speak your language now
we actually fail our way to the top we
don't we don't you know what I mean it's
constantly that overcoming of getting to
the top but it's building on those
failures and looking at it with a
different perspective so for me when
something doesn't work out I say Why
didn't it work out what can I do
differently what's an area of
opportunity here and you you dig into
that a little bit deeper and don't hold
that down to your heart like
there's a quote that says don't let
success get to your head and failure to
your heart you got to be resilient as as
an entrepreneur resilience and not
taking things to heart will the quicker
that you get up is the quicker that you
will
move well wow and and I I I agree
wholeheartedly and I think that um
reason why we have failure um is due to
the fact that we can't see the future
none of us can you know if we had the
magic if we had the Magic Bullet uh for
everything that we did you know we would
we wouldn't be talking right now we
would be you know doing crazy things but
I think that um the the reality is is
that we can't tell the future you are
bound to fail um in some degree or
you're bound to
misstep um you know sometimes we have
great guesses but you know we are I
think the whole thing about
entrepreneurialism is developing your
core developing yourself so that you
Flatline through the Peaks and valleys
of your lives because Peaks and valleys
have problems on both
sides you know you just keep going
through I mean there was a long time
even till now like where I eat lentil
peas a lot you know and and I I eat I
live like I'm poor you know during the
times where there's low cash flow and
during times where there's High cash
flow because I never know what's going
to happen in the future and maybe I
could live a little you know maybe go
out and eat at a fancy restaurant but I
always I always try to you know
um I I like to be frugal because I want
to be in that place where I can respond
to a crises or if someone dies that I
can go and and and and help someone out
you know I'm I'm not an entrepreneur so
that I can spend all my money that's not
the whole point of it and I think that
um uh just being able to Flatline
through everything gives me that
stability and it allows me to have
longevity right because if I'm too
extreme with my life in any way in in in
um you know in terms of spending or if
I'm I'm too extreme and just working so
hard you know you're going to lose right
so moderation definitely in how you
spend your energy is
key yeah and even just to add to that
the amount of stress that we're able to
deal with our in our life is often how
much can you handle that is not
predictable that is not certain that is
not set in stone because often times
being an entrepreneur being a parent for
that matter is unpredictable it's
there's circumstances that we just can't
control and the when you realize um
actually there's something that Tony
Robbins was saying a little while ago he
said the problem that we have with
problems is that we think that we
shouldn't have any
and it's it's funny because we only want
the problems that we want to have we
only want the uncertainty or the the
um that just ability of not knowing
what's going on or that that failures we
only want the failures that we like not
the ones that we we receive all the time
so it's kind of it's looking at that
with a certain set of eyes and being
able to control the situation that is
you we're always able to control ourself
and as a choice so on some of these uh
yeah let's there's so many comments you
guys are awesome if you're finding any
value in this please share this out I'm
excited to chat with you all
wow there's so many
people waade so interested in your
Insight on this how do you tune out or
deal with outside drama that crosses
your path in your daily life that is
awesome that is something that takes
time and I'll be real and honest with it
because there's several things that I'll
talk about with this one
um the person that I am
today is because of the daily practices
that I did to build this person that I
am today and it doesn't happen overnight
so if you look at the most successful
people in the world they all have
morning rituals that they do they and
this ritual might be meditation it might
be listening to an audio book it might
be meditating it might be praying it
might be connecting to your spiritual
self it might be um doing any of those
things
and it's
knowing how to deal with negativity in
your life in a positive way that doesn't
let anything penetrate you and from that
for me in my journey it became that I
dug really deep within myself in
figuring out who I was so when somebody
told me that I wasn't or drama came my
way um there's two things that you can
do there is one that you de with it
because there's somebody that you know
you have to deal with that and two
there's been a lot of toxic people that
are no longer in my life anymore because
we are the average of the five people we
spend the most time with so as you grow
and evolve there are going to PE there's
people here for a season a lifetime and
a reason and
determining what kind of person that
person is will really help you because
there's been a lot of people that I
thought you know this person's here for
a lifetime
but they weren't they were here for a
reason and a season in my life and
that's okay not everybody is going to go
on that Journey with you and it doesn't
mean that you don't care it just means
that you care about yourself more do you
find that you that um on a constant
basis you're screening your friends and
trying to you know you're constantly
placing the people that are going to
continue to give you that positivity or
has it has it leveled itself out you
know now that you've been in a certain
place do only attract the people that
you want to be
around I think that like attracts like
and um you you do you attract the people
that are on similar paths to you hence
the reason why me and you connected
right so you do definitely attract the
people that are on the same Mission and
path in your life but also if you're
just starting on your journey and you're
really changing as a human being and as
as you grow into this person that you're
meant to
you're going to see a lot and that's the
thing that a lot of people don't
understand is for me when I first
started on this journey I I gained
friends I lost friends I I ended
relationships so many things happened
but they were absolutely necessary and
some of them were extremely painful some
of them were very like a sigh of relief
but ultimately it it did level itself
out and one thing that I always share
with people is uh pay attention to the
people that don't clap when you succeed
everyone wants to pay attention to the
people that clap but for me one of the
biggest things is as I Rose and um it
really shows you who your people are who
are your tribe who are the people that
are really in your corner and the people
that you hold on to are the ones that
when you're 10 times better are 10 times
worse than what you are because the life
of an entrepreneur is like up and down
and it goes everywhere right and um so I
don't know if that helps answer your
question most definitely and but it's
funny you say playay attention to those
who clap and I I really believe that Who
Don't Clap That That Don't Clap a big
thing for me huge you know because I've
had that even happening with the hustle
Zone and so many people have either
unfriended me or they've uh you know
ignored my broadcast even though they
were going well and even people I was
working with last week just didn't want
to be friends with me this week and
because it's it's like it's very
competitive um however you know as a
spiritualist I'm someone that is not
attached to anyone or anything I've I've
detached from the world you know I've
detached from all um outcomes and I've
detached from from action I
love right CU you have when you detach
yourself yeah there's got to be a level
that you you stay connected but you
detach yourself from certain outcomes
sometimes there's a vision that you need
for your life but you need to be able to
have that flexibility to detach that you
know this is where I'm going and there's
certain things that you you have to be
able to detach and then also attach
yourself too and I love that you said
that we often give ourselves away we
often give our friends away we it's like
you know I I was talking about Karma a
lot of people think karma is just if I
do something it's going to come back to
me and that's not necessarily true Karma
means action and every time we take an
action it creates a vibration you know
and everyone resonate around you and if
we're not constantly taking action if
we're not constantly exchanging things
and giving things back to the world cuz
sometimes we got to give our friends to
the world we got to give our friends to
other people in order for us to move
forward because we can't there's only so
much that we can take on said right so I
I I honestly believe that it's just like
we often have to if we really want to
walk we can't have too much on our
shoulders at any given time and we may
have to lose close family friends we may
have to lose even our relationships with
our own children it's as as far as you
want to go um and some some people have
their barriers I do have mine and I
think that we like it's again this is
this is a canvas we can paint whatever
we want you know however we want we
could stop at any time and not feel
regretful that we didn't have to like
you know push forward do do do you agree
with
that sorry you cut out that I just H the
last yeah I said do you agree with that
like do you agree that you were
constantly having to shed just
anything and um I guess what was my
question yeah like do you do you agree
with having to shed a lot for the growth
you do because you're shedding the old
and becoming the new so the person that
I was five years ago and that person
that knew me five years ago if they
didn't see me for five years and see me
today which happens often they're like
oh my gosh like what did you you're
totally different you do you shed the
old to bring in the new you got to get
rid of the old to make room for the new
and that is with life and sometimes with
people and I know that's a little bit
you know so it's a sensitive topic for
people but I think
ultimately that shedding will reveal
itself to you in your life and you won't
need to you won't need somebody to tell
you if you're listening to this message
right now and you're
saying you know what I kind of feel that
way about somebody it's not me giving
you the answer the answers are already
within you and you know that and there's
going to be a lot of things that happen
around that you know you know this is
not the person for me this is not the
situation that I need to be in and you
can make a decision based on that
because I do believe that all those
answers are truly within you you just
need to unveil them now I'm going to
switch the questions a little bit and I
want to ask um what do you do for
fun oh that's so awesome so to be honest
I do a lot of things I love shopping I
love to travel my biggest thing is
traveling I I I love travel I I could
travel all day I think it's the best
thing in the world I want to see every
part of this wonderful Earth
and help as many people as I can all
over the world so for me if you could
say Leah what could you do that would
bring you so much travel spending time
with my family uh being with my kids and
to be honest I love working it's not
work to me it's a lifestyle to me it's
um it's fun to me I know that sounds
really weird for some other people but
for me like I stayed up last night till
2:30 in the morning and I was in full
full-blown creation mode of what I want
to give to other people and I woke up
this morning at 6:30 and I'm just fired
up ready to go and to me that's that's
fun so I do a lot of things for fun I
love going traveling and shopping and
going out for dinner and different
things like that but I truly love like
what lights me up is building a business
and teaching others how to be their best
self awesome what's your pet what's your
pet peeve
um I have a few with what like what I
don't like it when I don't like when
people aren't authentic I don't like uh
I don't like lying um
inauthenticity yeah I would say that
nice and what is it what's your favorite
dish that you like to
eat o I'm vegan so um it sounds crazy
but I don't eat a ton of salads but when
I go to a restaurant and I get this like
amazing salad I I love it but um but I
love like stir fries and and things like
that are you a good cook do you cook for
yourself I do I do I hope to say I'm a
good cook I'm I'm I'm pretty decent yeah
now I do I cook with the with the um
with your kids what do you tell them
about wealth and and what what what kind
of lessons do you teach them about money
oo wealth is in money wealth is in
financial wealth or wealth is in wealth
it could be abroad or you can get
specific I'm gon to go abroad so with my
kids um I teach them and this isn't
something that I actually love to share
is I spend a lot of time on personal
development in one year I spend even
over nearly $20,000 on personal
development so like I go to a lot of
things and I get all of that information
and that knowledge too and the biggest
thing that sometimes as entrepreneur
rurs is we don't always pass that down
to our children which is something that
I want my kids to to to understand so
wealth is happiness it's love it's
Financial abundance and it's
truly health wealth happiness love
fulfillment um and success so there's a
there's a beautiful thing about what
fulfills you is going to be different
from what fulfills me and I teach my
kids to truly like follow your heart and
stay true to who you are don't let the
world tell you who you are um I allow
them to be very expressive to be thems
and to be confident in who they are so I
teach them that you know the core
principles of how we raise our like how
I raise my kids is based in love and
happiness and I know that sounds very
basic but it's really not it's really
not yeah yeah yeah I agree with you and
uh do you spoil kids like are they
spoiled do you do you shower them with
gifts and or are you in the middle or do
you I shower them with my present so
like my like literally like what I mean
by that is um there's a different kind
of love and I love that book The Five
Love Languages yes but for me like I
truly believe like that undivided
attention that you get from either your
significant other or if you're a parent
when you give when the when your
children grow up they're going to
remember the times that you spent with
them they're going to remember those
moments that you know you didn't have
any makeup on you looked like crap and
you were working all night but yet you
woke up and you took them to the park
and you were running around with them
for two hours that's the kind of stuff
that I love to do with my kids just to
and whatever makes them happy my oldest
for example she loves having movie
nights so we totally do the movie night
thing so um it it is a little bit of
both but I don't spoil them with like
stuff I want them to have substance not
stuff wow great parent and I'm I'm the
same way with my son I I I honestly want
him to be his true self and he was like
I'm like you could be whatever you want
to be he wakes me up and he's like Daddy
I want to be a I want to be
famous like oh Lord okay so uh you know
but dig into the reasons why
right yeah I'm like what do I do but he
he he he he did a a fashion show and it
was pretty awesome to see him you know
he was strutting himself and he was
doing Michael Jackson he had the whole
crowd roaring but it was amazing to see
him living his truth because you know
today he may want to be famous tomorrow
he may want to be an engineer but we as
parents just have to make sure that we
give them the quality time and also give
them the support I think the support of
them being their their true selves I
think that means so much to their
happiness and their well-being so you
know so and it does a lot to their
confidence just to know that like when
you build that confidence as a child you
don't have to undo it as an adult they
have that you know what I mean yes true
love wow I love what you just said wow
so uh where can we find
you you can find me at Soulful Hustlers
dcom I'm going to be releasing some
really exciting stuff coming up in the
new year and I have some programs and
stuff so you can definitely check me out
there you can send me a message I'm
happy to reply to you would love to
connect with all of you if there's any
questions or things that I can help
answer please don't hesitate to reach
out okay well Leah thank you so much for
for coming into the hustle Zone thank
you for having me Ryan it's been so
great this was a great interview and uh
like I folks I just want want to tell
you this that every
time you know we we start our Journeys
to whatever whether it's going back to
school there has to be you you have to
be good to yourself and I often say on
my shows that you got to have two good
relationships one good relationship with
yourself and the other with your pillow
because you have to sleep at night right
and if you are not sleeping at night
that you don't have a good relationship
with yourself right
so right so what Leah is telling you is
that you got to have that good
relationship and you're so I I really
like your presence and I hope we can
work together and do some other projects
together because you're so grounded as
an entrepreneur it just it it I just
like being um uh immersed with your
presence in in a sense that oh you're so
sweet yeah this was awesome this is
awesome because there's there's
different types of energy and I think
that if I'm you know and especially when
there's uh when there's there's um the
hustle energy is necessary because
sometimes you need
to oh my gosh yes it's it's it's
necessary but we also need to have that
balance um in just how we treat like
it's just it's a lot of things it's like
how we treat our children that inter
connection it's it's all of that it's
all of that so anyway we could be here
all day but thank you so much we good I
can you righto
we'll have to do part two yes we'll do
part two okay everyone folks tell me do
you guys want to see a part two uh do
you want to see two guys so one for yes
two for no so let us know and uh we're
going to answer your questions after the
live is done and please folks this is
this is one of those hustle SES that you
have to share share share share share
share share so I'm going to leave you
guys with this welcome to
the hustles all
let's do it
again let's do that one more time so
welcome to the one more time okay H Zone
hustle Zone awesome so anyways I'll talk
to you guys later and tune in um we
don't I I don't plan any of this because
honestly that's the best part though I
love the live stuff yeah it's just
there's a a natural energy about it
there's more it's more organic and and I
hate planning these shows out because
it's not fair to the audience I the I
don't do it either I don't do well with
scripts yeah so me neither I like this
it's good but this was good so we're
going to work on a part two maybe we can
collaborate and we can you know do
something but let's talk offline uh it's
it's it was a pleasure